Guide to the Yale Alumni Activities Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale alumni activities photographs
1889-1994
RU 754
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.75
(10 boxes)
The photographs document alumni dinners, awards ceremonies, and various regional club activities.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 8-D (YRG 8-D), Audio-visual materials documenting Yale alumni activities.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The photographs are arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The photographs document alumni dinners, awards ceremonies, and various regional club activities.
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Photographs; AYA (Organization); Yale University -- Alumnae and alumnae -- Societies, etc.
- Photographs documenting alumni activities, 1889-1973; Series I
  - Alumni Day
    - 1918 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1937 (Rudy Vallee) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1938-1940 (negatives) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1957 (Law) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - No date (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Board
  - Conference of Secretaries, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Board and Corporation meetings and lunches, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Convocation--Lawrence Lecture, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Chicago Trip, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Clubs
  - Boston, 1924-1941 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - California, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Chicago
      - 1900, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - 1925-1932 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - 1939-1947, no date (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Colorado
      - 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - National Alumni Meeting at Denver, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Connecticut
      - Bristol, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Fairfield County, Plainfield, Waterbury, 1889-1938 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Greenwich, Hartford, New Britain, New Haven, 1916-1939 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Delaware, 1941 May (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Detroit, 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Kansas, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Minneapolis, 1934, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - New Jersey, Montclair, 1924, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - New York
      - Bachelor dinner for Holland S. Duell, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - 1925-1942 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Artwork, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - St. Anthony's Club of New York City dinner, 1962 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Northeast Federation of Yale Clubs, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Northwest Alumni Federation, 1937-1942 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Ohio--Cleveland, Cincinnati, 1937-1941 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Oklahoma, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Pacific--Honolulu, Manila, British Columbia, 1936-1951 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Pennsylvania--Pittsburgh, Philadelphia, 1921, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Seattle, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - South--Florida, Tennessee, Georgia, 1938-1941 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - St. Louis, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - St. Louis National Meeting, 1967 June (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Texas--Fort Worth, Dallas, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Utah, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Washington, D.C.--dinners, 1934, 1941, 1954-1957 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Washington, D.C.--railroad outing, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Wisconsin, 1938-1940 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous, 1939, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Association of Class Officers
    - Dinners 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Convocation, 1966 October (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Dinners
    - 1910 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - circa 1912 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - United Graduates Reunion Dinner, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Mory's, 1939 May 22 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - 1940-1944 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Campbell Dinner, 1942 January (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Harvard-Princeton dinner (Montreal), 1947 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - 1951 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Dinner for Kingman Brewster, Jr., circa 1960s (Box 4, Folder 66 - 67)
    - Unidentified and undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Publications--Alumni Weekly, first Board (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Reunions
    - Contact sheets, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Class of 1934, 55th reunion, 1989 May (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Class of 1939, 50th reunion, 1989 May (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Class of 1944, 45th reunion, 1989 May (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Class of 1969, 20th reunion, 1989 May (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Class of 1974, 15th reunion, 1989 May (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Class of 1945, 45th reunion, 1990 May (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Class of 1965, 25th reunion, 1990 May (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Class of 1985, 5th reunion, 1990 May (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Class of 1927, 65th reunion, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Class of 1932, 60th reunion, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Class of 1937, 65th reunion, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Class of 1947, 55th reunion, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Class of 1957, 35th reunion, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Class of 1962, 30th reunion, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Class of 1967, 25th reunion, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Class of 1972, 20th reunion, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Class of 1982, 15th reunion, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 82-83)
    - Yale Hillel Forum, 1992 May (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Class of 1928, 65th reunion, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Class of 1933, 60th reunion, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Class of 1938, 55th reunion, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Class of 1943, 50th reunion, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Class of 1948, 45th reunion, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Class of 1953, 40th reunion, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Class of 1968, 25th reunion, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Class of 1983, 10th reunion, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 May (Box 6, Folder 93 - 95)
    - Seminar, 1994 May (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 May (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Seminars
    - Summer, 1959
    - Assembly I, 1972 November 2-4 (Box 4, Folder 98)
      - Assembly calendar, contact sheets (Box 4, Folder 99)
      - Board: seminar, forums (Box 4, Folder 100)
      - Board: seminar, forums, individual speakers (Box 4, Folder 101)
      - Social events (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Assembly II, 1973 April 13-14
      - Assembly calendar, contact sheets (Box 4, Folder 103)
      - Seminars (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Assembly and convocation, 1973 October
      - Cocktail party (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Contact sheets (Box 5, Folder 106)
      - Luncheons/dinners (Box 5, Folder 107)
      - Seminars/forums (Box 5, Folder 108)
      - Social events (Box 5, Folder 109)
      - Seminars, undated (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Folio
    - Alumni Dinners, 1909-1910 (Box DR1F4)
    - Alumni Dinners, 1912-1927 (Box DR2F5)
    - Alumni Clubs
      - Association of Southern Yale Clubs at Mount Vernon, VA, and Washington, DC, 1921 (Box DR2F10)
      - Yale Club of Boston with President Taft (Box DR35F97)
      - Associated Western Yale Clubs: 12th Annual Meeting, Kansas City, MO; 16th Annual Meeting, Pittsburgh, PA, 1915, 1921 (Box DR35F97)
- Photographs of Yale reunions, circa 1980s-1990s; Accession 2010-A-052
  - Photographs of Yale reunions, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 1)